[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, if the poorest 3.5 billion people in the world added all their money together, it would be _____ than all the money of the richest 85 people in the world.",
        "answer": "less than"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of a type of public transportation commonly used in cities?",
        "answer": "helicopters"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, which of the following groups would NOT be considered as “underprivileged”?",
        "answer": "men with high education levels"
    },
    {
        "question": "The article says, “It isn’t always as simple as ‘Try harder!’ or ‘Just get a better job!’” What does this mean?",
        "answer": "It may not be as easy for some groups of people to improve their lives as it is for others."
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? Based on the definition used in the article, social inequality refers to a situation where one group has an advantage over other groups because of differences in education, money or power.",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the example used for disabled workers, if twenty non-disabled people are unemployed, how many disabled people are likely unemployed?",
        "answer": "forty"
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? The definition of social inequality used in the article refers to a situation where some groups have more advantages than others.",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? The answers to the group of questions at the beginning of the article are all False.",
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the example used for disabled workers, if twenty disabled people are unemployed, how many non-disabled people are likely unemployed?",
        "answer": "ten"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, people who can get to green spaces have _____ than those who cannot visit green spaces.",
        "answer": "better physical and mental health"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, which of the following groups would NOT be considered as “privileged”?",
        "answer": "disabled people"
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? The answers to the group of questions at the beginning of the article are all True.",
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, if the richest 85 people in the world added all their money together, it would be _____ than all the money of the poorest half of the people in the world.",
        "answer": "more than"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a type of public transportation commonly used in cities?",
        "answer": "subways"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, the number of women elected to high governmental positions in Taiwan is _____ other places in Asia.",
        "answer": "higher than"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not an example of the “working poor” mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "People who are employed and paid well enough that they can easily pay for their lifestyle."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, other places in Asia have _____ women elected to high governmental positions than Taiwan does.",
        "answer": "fewer"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, poorer people who can get to _____ can improve their health by as much as forty percent.",
        "answer": "green spaces"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is closest in meaning to the “working poor” mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "People who are employed but paid such low wages that they cannot afford many of their basic needs."
    }
]